Guide to the Office of the Registrar, Faculty of Arts and Sciences, Yale University, Student Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Student grade lists, 2004-2007; Accession 2009-A-217
  - College Seminars, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 434)
  - Computer Science, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 435)
  - Drama School, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 437)
  - Directed Studies (Literature), Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 438)
  - East Asian Studies, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 439)
  - Ecology and Evolutionary Biology, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 440)
  - Economics, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 441)
  - Electrical Engineering, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 442)
  - Engineering and Applied Science, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 443)
  - English, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 444)
  - Environmental Studies, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 445)
  - Film Studies, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 446)
  - Forestry and Environmental Studies, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 447)
  - French, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 448)
  - Geology and Geophysics, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 449)
  - German, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 450)
  - Hindi, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 451)
  - History, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 452)
  - History of Art, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 453)
  - Humanities, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 454)
  - International Studies, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 455)
  - Italian, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 456)
  - Japanese, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 457)
  - Judaic Studies, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 458)
  - Latin, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 459)
  - Latin American Studies, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 460)
  - Law School, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 461)
  - Linguistics, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 462)
  - Literature, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 463)
  - Math, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 464)
  - MCDB, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 465)
  - Modern Greek, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 466)
  - Music, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 467)
  - Music School, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 468)
  - Near East Languages, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 469)
  - Neuroscience, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 470)
  - Philosophy, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 471)
  - Physics, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 472)
  - Political Science, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 473)
  - Portuguese, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 474)
  - Psychology, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 475)
  - Religious Studies, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 476)
  - Religious Studies (GS), Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 477)
  - Russian, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 478)
  - Science, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 479)
  - Sociology, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 480)
  - Spanish, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 481)
  - Special Divisional, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 482)
  - Statistics, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 483)
  - Study of the City, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 484)
  - Swah, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 485)
  - Theater Studies, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 486)
  - Vietnamese, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 487)
  - Women Gender and Sexual Studies, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 488)
- Yale College student records, 1903-1996; 1960-1979; Accession 2013-A-073
  Restricted until January 1, 2071